rsvlts.com 2017-01-04

# Privacy Policy – The Roosevelts

UPDATED June 2, 2014

**Privacy  Policy**

The Roosevelts knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers The Roosevelts’s treatment of personal information that The Roosevelts gathers when you are on the The Roosevelts website and when you use The Roosevelts services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that The Roosevelts does not own or control, or to individuals that The Roosevelts does not employ or manage.

**Information Collected by The Roosevelts**

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our The Roosevelts users:

1\. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

2\. Automatic Information:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. The Roosevelts and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, The Roosevelts cookie information, and the page you requested. The Roosevelts uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.  
o The Roosevelts may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While The Roosevelts will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

**E-mail Communications**

The Roosevelts is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the “Sharing Your Information” section below. The Roosevelts may send out e-mails with The Roosevelts-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.

**Cookies**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. The Roosevelts cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.

The “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of The Roosevelts’s coolest features.

The Roosevelts’s advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads.  If you would prefer to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our advertising partner Platform-A’s privacy policy and opt-out page.

**Sharing Your Information  **

Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.

The Roosevelts Personnel: The Roosevelts personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of The Roosevelts business.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if The Roosevelts, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.

Protection of The Roosevelts and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of *******, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Syndication: The Roosevelts allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the The Roosevelts website.

With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.

**Copyright Information**  
All images on RSVLTS.com are readily available in various places on the Internet and believed to be in public domain. Images posted are believed to be posted within our rights according to the U.S. Copyright Fair Use Act (title 17, U.S. Code.)  
If you believe that any content appearing on RSVLTS.com infringes on your copyright, please let us know. E-Mail tips[at]gmail[dot]com following information to us and the infringing material will be removed as soon as possible.  
(a) your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address;  
(b) a description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;  
(c) the exact URL or a description of each place where alleged infringing material is located;  
(d) a statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use has not been authorized by you, your agent, or the law;  
(e) your electronic or physical signature or the electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on your behalf; and  
(f) a statement by you made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate, that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf  
Please also note that under Section 512(f) of the Copyright Act any person who knowingly materially misrepresents that material or activity is infringing may be subject to liability.

**Links**

RSVLTS.com contain links to other sites. Please be aware that RSVLTS.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by RSVLTS.com.

**Changes to this  Privacy Policy**

The Roosevelts may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to thePrivacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the The Roosevelts website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

**Conditions of Use**

If you decide to visit The Roosevelts website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

**Effective Date of this  Privacy Policy **

This Privacy Policy is effective as of July 18, 2012 and last updated July 18, 2012.
